mobpartner.com 2018-07-21

# Privacy Policy - MobPartner

All data supplied by the User to MOBPARTNER, including his IP address, are stored in MOBPARTNER’s transactional platform database, and are handled with the utmost care regarding confidentiality issues. The User guarantees that the information supplied to MOBPARTNER is accurate and up-to-date, and that any relevant change will be communicated within the best timeframe.

The User’s individual personal information may also be used by MOBPARTNER in order to communicate information related to the Service. In no case will it be provided to any third party for commercial means without the User’s consent beforehand.

In accordance with E.U. Directive 95/46/EC, the User has the right to access and update its invididual personal information, either directly online on MOBPARTNER’s website ([www.cheetahmedialink.com](http://www.cheetahmedialink.com/)) or through MOBPARTNER’s Support Center (<http://support.mobpartner.com/home>). Should the User refuse that his individual personal information is processed for any purpose, or only for commercial means, he may then contact MOBPARTNER’s Support Center with his proper reference and ID.

The Service is conceived to follow laws, guidelines and standards concerning the protection of personal information. In order to provide the Services, the website uses cookies whose only purpose is to flag each User’s connections. These cookies are only used in order to improve the Service provided to each User. Should the User refuse these cookies (for instance via his web browser), then MOBPARTNER will not be in a position to guarantee the performance of the complete set of functionalities offered by its Service.

Regarding our RTB activities please refer to this page :  
<http://www.cheetahmedialink.com/rtb-privacy-policy/>
